I knew it...
It's coming!
The Female Titan!
The Female Titan emerged once more,
defeating the elite Squad Levi members,
one after the next.
I will kill it!
Having decided it was his fault for
believing in his companions,
Eren transforms and engages
the Female Titan.
but he suffers defeat, and the
Female Titan takes him.
Give Eren back!
No matter where she goes, I'll kill her,
rip her apart,
and get you out of that filth.
I'm sorry, Eren...
Just wait a little longer...
Wait!
Wh-What are you...
Fall back for now.
The Defeated
57th Expedition Beyond the Walls (6)
Maintain this distance.
It may be tired.
It does not appear to
be going very fast.
He seems to have been bitten
right out of the neck.
Is Eren dead?
He's alive.
The target appears intelligent,
and its goal seems to be capturing Eren.
If it wanted him dead,
it would've crushed him.
The target is fighting to
escape after going through
the trouble of putting him in its mouth.
Its goal may have been to eat Eren.
If that's the case, he's in its stomach.
It's more reasonable to
assume that he's dead.
He's alive!
I hope you're right.
If you'd only protected Eren,
this wouldn't have happened!
I see...
You're the one from back then.
Eren's close friend?
We'll limit ourselves to a single goal.
First, give up on killing
the Female Titan.
It killed many of our comrades!
As long as it can harden
its skin, we can't kill it.
Do as I say.
We'll pin our hopes on
Eren still being alive,
and rescue him before
it leaves the forest.
I will tear away at it...
You draw its attention!
He's fast...
So fast that it has no
time to harden its skin!
We can go for the neck...
It's tired...
I bet it can't move!
I can kill it!
Stop!
Eren!
Hey!
We're getting out of here!
Eren...
I think he's okay...
He's alive!
But filthy.
Forget about it...
We'll retreat.
Don't lose sight of the core objective.
Is it more important
to get what you want?
Isn't he an important friend?
No, I...
They're already coming back?
What happened?
No idea...
But I bet they're bringing plenty
of dead bodies with them again.
Eldo is coming home.
I see.
Think Oluo will have time to come home?
It wouldn't hurt to make
him dinner, just in case.
Gunther's coming back.
I see.
This is the part I never get used to.
No one does.
How are my friends going to die?
How am I going to die?
It's all you can think about.
I try not to dwell on it.
If I pictured how I'm going to die,
I probably wouldn't be able to fight.
Yeah.
You're right.
How long will I stay alive?
You're alive now, aren't you?
For now.
Isn't that a good thing?
You're alive!
Can you say that in front of
the bodies of those who aren't?
I might not be able
to go home anymore...
We're almost done.
There were about five
dead we couldn't recover.
Not even a part of them?
They're the only ones we
couldn't due to the Titans...
It's probably best for the families
that we not bring those back.
Say they're MIA.
Yes, sir.
We saw several Titans near the forest,
but none are headed this way as of yet.
We're moving out now.
Tell all the squads.
Yes, sir.
I cannot accept this, Commander Erwin!
Hey, you...
We should recover them!
Ivan's body was right in front of us!
There was a Titan right next to him...
It could result in another casualty!
If they attack, we can just defeat them!
Ivan's an old friend.
We're from the same town.
I know his parents.
If nothing else, I'd
like to bring him home!
Don't be selfish!
Squabbling kids?
Captain Levi...
If you confirmed he's
dead, that's enough.
Whether you have the body, dead is dead.
It won't change anything.
No...
We'll say Ivan and the
others went missing.
That's my final decision.
Give it up.
Don't the two of you
have any human feelings at all?!
Hey, Dieter... You're going too far!
Information We Can Share So Far:
Survey Corps Wagons (1)
These wagons include a complicated suspension system
of ultra-hard steel that can only be made in factory cities.
Information We Can Share So Far:
Survey Corps Wagons (2)
Wagons hitched to Survey Corps horses travel
around 20 km/h. They can maintain their speed
on various terrain, be it paved or unpaved road.
Titans!
That's...
Dieter!
That fool...
The rear line has sighted Titans!
Onward at full speed!
I don't see any tall trees or buildings.
Fighting out here will be difficult.
We're better off outrunning
them till we reach the walls.
They're going to catch us!
Do we have to fight?
Maneuver Gear has limited
utility in open areas!
And look...
They just keep coming!
Then what do we do?
We...
No! They'll reach us!
I'll get behind them!
I'll draw their attention, then you—
No.
Just abandon the bodies.
They'll reach us.
B-But...
In the past, many bodies
haven't made it back.
These guys aren't anything special.
Are we doing this?
Are we really doing it?!
Damn it...
We have to!
Okay!
Keep going!
As soon as we know where
we are, we will depart.
Stay alert!
We'll have to slightly alter
our route to the east...
Captain Levi...
I...
This proves that they were alive.
To me, at least.
This was Ivan's.
Captain...
We're leaving!
Eren, you should stop
considering the Survey Corps.
What? You're going to tell
me they're stupid, too?
That isn't it...
The Survey Corps is back!
The front gate's opening!
Let's go, Mikasa!
The heroes are back!
These are all that made it back?
Everyone else must've been eaten.
That's what happens when
you go outside the walls.
It's like our taxes all
go to fatten them up.
Eren?
What's wrong?
Eren...
Eren!
You shouldn't get up.
Rest.
The Female Titan?
It got away.
Why?
What about the others?
What about the plan?
It failed...
Rest for the time being.
What is this?
Did you save me again?
We're almost to the walls.
Aren't there fewer than
there were this morning?
Man...
Far fewer...
Another disaster.
Just this morning, they left raising a ruckus,
but they're already back?
What was the point?
Who knows?
But judging by the gloomy expressions,
they managed to waste more
of our taxes, if nothing else.
Eren, just bear with it.
So cool!
The Survey Corps is so awesome!
They got the crap kicked out
of them, and they still fight!
Captain Levi!
My daughter is in your squad...
I'm Petra's father.
Before she sees me, I
wanted to talk to you.
She sent me this letter...
She mentioned that you respected her
abilities enough to let her join your squad.
That she was going to devote herself to you.
Well, I guess she's too starry-eyed
to consider how her father feels!
Well, as her father,
I think it's too early for her to marry.
She's still so young, with
so much to experience...
Commander Erwin! Answer us!
Did this expedition learn enough
to justify the number of dead?
Do you think the dead have no regrets?
The expenses and casualties from
the expedition were more than enough
to discredit the faction that had
supported the Survey Corps.
As those responsible, including Erwin,
were summoned to the capital,
it was decided that Eren
was to be handed over.
That day, Annie was part
of the escort guard for Eren and the others,
as they answered a summons to the capital.
Suddenly, Armin appeared,
and asked Annie to assist with
a highly sensitive mission.
Smile
Raid on Stohess District (1)